governmentsecurity.org 2011-06-30

# GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org Privacy Policy | GSO - Network Security Resources

GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org. takes your privacy seriously so we have created this privacy statement ("Privacy Policy") in order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy.

We self-certify compliance with:

GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org respects individual privacy and values the confidence of its customers, employees, business partners and others. We strive to collect, use and disclose personal information in a manner consistent with the highest ethical standards and in accordance with the laws of the countries in which it does business.

By accessing the GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org website at www.GovernmentSecurity.org, including all related pages ("Site"), and any subscription based features or services offered by GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org either through the Site or by other means, (collectively, the "Service"), you are accepting the practices outlined in this Statement.

### What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org' collection of personal information that we gather when you are on the Site and when you use the Service.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org does not own or control, or to individuals that GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org does not employ or manage. For avoidance of doubt, this Privacy Policy does not apply to any third party information gathered by GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org' subscribers when they use the Service. It only applies to information gathered by GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org to provide the Service to its subscribers.

### What Personal Information About Customers Does GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org Collect?

Our primary goal in collecting information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from our customers:

### Information You Provide to Us:

GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org collects identifying information when you use the Service, when you visit the Site (including, without limitation, any GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org.com web pages or landing pages), and when you enter promotions or contests. For example, we require customers who register to use the Service to give us the following personal information: their name, company name, address, phone number, and e-mail address, and financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, and the identity of users within the organization that will be using the Service. We also require that you provide us with your Salesforce.com login credentials in order for us to access your sales data information and deliver the Service to you. When you initially express interest obtaining additional information about the Service, or when you register for the Service, we may also ask for additional types of personal information, such as title, department name, fax number, or additional company information. We may also request demographic information and unique identifiers in order to provide you with a more personalized experience or verify your passwords.

All financial and billing information that we collect from you is used for the purposes of checking your qualifications as a prospective customer and billing you for the Service. Such billing information is not used by GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org for marketing or promotional purposes. GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org may use a third-party intermediary to manage the credit card and billing processing. This intermediary is solely a link in the distribution chain, and is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information provided, except for the sole purpose of credit card and billing processing.

Customers will be use the Service to analyze their sales data ("Customer Data"). GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org will not review, share, distribute, print, or reference any such Customer Data except as provided for in the Service Agreement or as may be required by law. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Customer Data may at times be viewed or accessed by GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issue, or for investigating a suspected violation of the Service Agreement, or as may be required by law.

### Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via our website. GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org automatically receives and records certain "traffic data" on our server logs including your IP address, GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org cookie information, the page you requested, and your communications and interactions with other site registrants. GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the Service.

We automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and use of components of our Service. We may use this information to provide research, advice and information, including, without limitation, for benchmarking purposes (e.g. we may publish an industry white paper that uses data collected through the use of our Service). This data is only used in the aggregate. This type of collective data also enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Service so we can make the Service more useful to as many customers as possible. In addition, we may provide statistical information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our Site and Service. We may share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use areas of our Site and our Service, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal experience.

We also collect and use information for internal purposes. For example, if you are a registered user of the GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org' subscription-based Service, we may keep records in your account history of your complaints about other registered users online behavior, and any reported violation of our Service Agreement that you or someone on your account may have committed.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit web sites anonymously. While GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

### E-mail Communications:

We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org if your computer supports this type of program, in order to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful. We may also send out emails with information regarding GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org or our partners including promotions and events. Customers can opt out of being contacted by us by sending an email to support@GSO Management- GovernmentSecurity.org.com.

### Information From Other Sources:

For purposes such as improving personalization of our Service, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

### What about Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org may employ cookies in order for its server to recognize a return visitor as a unique user. The cookies placed by the GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org server are readable only by GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org, and cookies cannot access, read or modify any other data on a computer.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org' most attractive features.

### Will GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org Share Any of the Information it Receives?

Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only with entities that are controlled or controlled by or under common control of GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org and as described below:

### Affiliated Business We Do Not Control:

We are affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses operate within the Service or through the Site. In other situations, GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org provides other services, or sells products or services jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share customer information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.

### Third Party Sites

The Service may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org site. These other websites are not under GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org of those other websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org site are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

### Agents:

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and may need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples may include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. We may also provide your personal information to agents who will use it to verify aggregate usage data that we provide to our partners.

### Promotional Offers:

We may send offers to certain customers on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you are a registered user of the GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org' subscription-based Service and do not wish to receive these offers, please send an email to support@GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org.com.

### Business Transfers:

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets or businesses. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, customer information would be one of the assets that are transferred.

### U.S. - EU Safe Harbor Privacy Statement:

For personal information received from you that GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org receives from the European Economic Area, GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org has committed to handling such information in accordance with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org' Safe Harbor certification can be found at<http://web.ita.doc.gov/safeharbor/shlist.nsf/webPages/safe+harbor+list>. For more information about the Safe Harbor Principles, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Website at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/SH_Overview.asp>.

### Protection of GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org and Others:

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### With Your Consent:

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties.

### Is Information About Me Secure?

Your GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org Account Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by signing off once you have finished using a shared computer.

Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.

### Can Children Use GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org' services?

Our site and the use of services made available through GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org are not intended for children under the age of 13. GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 13 and believes that children of any age should get their parents' consent before giving out any personal information. We encourage you to participate in your child's web experience. GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org recommends that parents use Web filtering technology to supervise their kids' access to the Web.

### Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit the GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org Site or Service, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of U.S. Federal and California state law.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

GSO Management - GovernmentSecurity.org may amend this Privacy Policy. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will notify you by posting the revised notice on our Site or sending you an email so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the privacy of your data on the Site or the Service, please email support@GSO Management- GovernmentSecurity.org.com. Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Privacy Policy Effective Date: January 27, 2010
